♪♪
I hate the way men look at you.
If men stop looking at me, I
don't pay my rent, Reverend.
We should've met at your place.
This was your choice.
Just remember,
my fee is the same
whether it's here or there.
I think our time's
just about up anyway.
Always a pleasure, Reverend.
May I see you next week?
You know where to reach me.
No, Tuesday's no good.
How about... Wednesday at 7:00?
David Campbell,
how can you say that?
You know you're my favorite.
You bet I'll prove it.
Hey, did I tell you...
Um, I listened to your
radio show the other day.
You give good advice, Doctor.
7:00 Wednesday.
Bye.
Had I known you were this
good, I would've voted for you.
What a man has to do
today to win one lousy vote.
Jeffrey.
Hmm?
I need your help with a
little problem I'm having.
Oh?
What's that?
Anything.
You know Ann Rawls?
Yeah.
She's, uh... what do
they call her nowadays?
Uh, your madam.
I may be wrong,
but I don't think
she wants me working
for her anymore.
Why would she want to
shoot herself in the foot?
You're the best she's got.
Yeah, well, um, I haven't
exactly been straight with her.
I mean, there have
been a few clients
I haven't told her about.
So? She's not the
only game in town.
No, but she's the
best game in town.
Most money, the best clients.
You will talk to her,
won't you, Jeffrey?
Well, um... Janie, I'm sorry.
I, uh... I can't do that.
I'm a state senator.
I, uh... I can't get involved
in anything like that.
I was hoping you
wouldn't disappoint me.
Janie?
What is that supposed to mean?
You have no idea how good
you sound on tape, Senator.
What the hell are
you talking about?
You know those little playful
telephone conversations
we've been having?
I've recorded them...
just in case you needed
a little motivation.
Senator, let me
ask you a question.
If one of your
people stole from you,
wouldn't you get rid of them?
Ann, I'm not condoning
what Janie did.
I'm here to ask you
for a personal favor.
Give her another chance, huh?
I can't, Senator.
I just don't trust her.
Besides, it would set a bad
example for my other girls.
Ann?
Hello, Janie.
Janie, I did what I could.
Her mind is made up.
Now, I want that tape.
Good-bye, Jeffrey.
Don't force my hand!
Maybe you should
go to the police.
It's quite something.
Your clients have been
parading in here all day
trying to get me
to change my mind.
First, David Campbell,
your radio psychologist
friend, dropped by.
Then I got a visit
from Reverend Phelps.
They both say
you taped all of your
conversations with them.
You're a bitch, Janie.
I've made you a
lot of money, Ann.
You're fired, Janie.
I have your entire
client list, Ann.
I'll give it to the press.
Get out of here, Janie.
There won't be a man in
Atlanta who'll touch your girls.
Why don't you give
me about 30 minutes?
I'm gonna take a bubble bath,
put on some lotion.
You are one naughty boy, Roger.
30 minutes.
Bye.
Jerk.
♪♪
How did you get in here?
What are you doing?
No! No!
Oh.
Janie?
Come on, Janie. It's Ann.
I want to talk to you.
Janie?
Oh.
Hey, Janie!
Sugar?
Come on, sugar.
What are you doing?
Why did you go to
Janie's apartment
in the first place?
- Well, earlier in the day...
- Mm-hmm.
She had threatened to
turn my girls' client list
over to the press.
- That would have put me out of business.
- Oh.
I was going to try and
talk some sense into her.
Maybe even give
her another chance.
Mm-hmm.
Uh, Lieutenant Brooks mentioned,
uh, an-an audio tape
that Janie had made.
What was that all about?
Oh, Janie was
putting the pressure
on three of her clients
to try and convince
me not to get rid of her.
Each of them paid me a visit.
Oh. Oh, oh. But they didn't...
they didn't convince you?
I'm a businesswoman,
Mr. Matlock.
Uh-huh.
Janie lied and stole from me.
I had to fire her.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, well...
What was... What
was on the tape?
Well, apparently,
she had taped several
explicit conversations
with each of them
that would prove embarrassing
if they were made public.
Oh, I see. I see. Boy...
it sure would be helpful
to get hold of that tape.
Does that mean you're
going to take the case?
Yeah, I think I will.
Thank you.
Has anyone ever told you
that you have the most
piercing blue eyes?
Uh, n-n-no, no,
I-I don't think so.
Tell you what.
Let's you and I
have dinner tonight.
Well, you're in jail.
Well, you'll take care of that.
I'll pay the bail
and then we can celebrate
our getting together.
Well, uh... no, no,
no-no-not tonight.
I mean, I've got a lot of work
to do... I mean, a lot of work.
Oh, what a shame.
Well, perhaps another time.
Hmm.
When you're not working.
À bientôt.
Uh, ma'am?
It's French.
It means "I'll be seeing you."
Oh, yeah, well... à
bientôt to you, too.
À bientôt.
Anybody figure out
how the killer got in?
Probably had a key.
Ann said Janie
had lost her keys.
Huh.
Mm-hmm.
I tell you what, Conrad...
You find that tape and
I'll buy you a fine dinner.
- Anywhere?
- Anywhere.
Now I'm motivated.
Yeah.
Nice, fat New York
steak smothered in onions,
baked potato with
sour cream and chives.
How'd you two get in here?
Oh, I... uh, the police
gave us this key.
Uh, I'm representing the woman
accused of killing Janie Ladd.
I'm Ben Matlock.
Uh-huh, and you?
Conrad McMasters.
And you?
Tom Marshall.
I'm the super.
I manage the building.
I'm just checking
out a few things,
seeing what needs to be done
before the owners
can rent it again.
Oh... we're looking
around a little ourselves.
Okay, well, suit yourself.
Yeah, I'm gonna
check the bedroom.
Yeah.
Did, uh, did you
know Janie Ladd well?
Not really.
She liked to keep to herself.
Mm-hmm.
Do you know what
she did for a living?
Yeah, she was a call girl.
Yeah.
Hey, she paid her rent
on the first of every month.
Well, I guess that's
better than some.
Oh, hell, I'm late for a
doctor's appointment.
Listen, can you do me a favor
and lock the door
when you leave?
- Yeah.
- Great, thanks.
It's not here, Ben.
Uh, well, we'll go with you.
Go with you.
Well, Conrad...
looks like you're going to pop
for that steak and
potatoes yourself.
Uh, did you call the police
the night she was killed?
No, I wasn't here.
I was at a family dinner.
By the time I got back, the
police had already shown up.
Oh, well...
- Good luck to you, Mr. Matlock.
- Thanks.
- Sure.
Huh?
Tom Marshall's
not on this registry.
Maybe he lives somewhere else.
Superintendent lives
in apartment 101.
His name's D. Harper.
Excuse me, I'm looking
for Dr. David Campbell.
I'm Dr. Campbell.
Oh.
Michelle Thomas, Doctor...
Ben Matlock's associate.
We're representing Ann Rawls.
Right, right.
This is Bert Ginsberg,
my station manager.
- Miss Thomas.
- Hello.
- Why don't we talk in my office?
- Okay.
- Bert, I'll see you at 7:00?
- You got it.
Thank you.
- You care for some coffee?
- No, thanks.
I take it Ann Rawls
told you about the tape.
Yes, she did.
You must think
quite poorly of me.
Well, I try not to judge
people, Dr. Campbell.
I'm sure you must have
been pretty frightened
when Janie told you
that your relationship with
her might be made public.
Miss Thomas...
I... am not capable of violence.
Where were you at 6:30
the evening Janie was
killed, Dr. Campbell?
Home.
Alone?
Yes, I'm afraid so.
My wife is an actress...
Blaine Campbell.
She's been on the road
for the last couple months
in a touring production.
Well, did you talk to anyone
who might be able to confirm
that you were home that evening?
Yes, I did, I was on the
phone most of the night.
With whom?
Some of my private patients.
I have a full schedule
of patients that I see.
Well, do you remember the person
you were speaking
to around 6:30?
Yes, I think so.
May I have the name, please?
No.
Excuse me?
Miss Thomas, I can't
divulge the name of a patient
without his permission.
It would be both unethical
and unprofessional of me.
I don't anticipate a problem,
but I'll have to
talk to him first
and then I'll get back to you.
I'll get it.
Hi.
Oh, hi, hi.
Co-Co-C-Come in, come in.
Uh, uh, uh... Miss Hawkins,
this is, uh, Madam Rawls.
Miss Rawls.
How do you do?
Miss Hawkins.
Thank you.
That'll be all?
Yes.
All right.
Come on in.
What, what, what
brings you way out here?
Well, now, I had a
message that you called...
Something about
"you had good news."
- Hmm.
- What's the good news?
Oh, oh, oh, th-the, the judge
who was assigned to your case
had to step down
because of illness.
Why is that good news?
Well, Judge Harris would
hang a jaywalker if he could.
He'd make our lives miserable.
Ken Harris.
You know him?
He's a client?
Judge Harris?
You'd think he'd smile more.
DMV just got back to me.
You know that car Tom
Marshall was driving?
Yeah?
It was rented.
Yeah, by whom?
A Mark Evans.
Is that supposed to ring a bell?
No, but his boss' name
should... Senator Jeffrey Paul.
Excuse me?
Well, well, well.
Well, well, well, well, well.
More and more good
news today, huh?
Hmm... I bet you're going
to have to get right on this.
Oh, you betcha.
Well, I guess I'll just go.
Okay.
Uh... but... you know...
you and I could
have dinner tonight.
I mean, you do
have a rain check.
Uh, well, well, I...
I ate such a late lunch that,
that I-I-I don't think I'd be
hungry for-for-for dinner.
Oh.
Well, I guess I'll just have
to catch you another time.
When you're... hungry.
À bientôt.
À-À bi... à bi...
à bi... À bientôt.
One thing I know
about my constituents...
If I was a gambler or a drunk,
there'd be all kinds
of compassion.
Yeah, but they find out
you're seeing a call girl,
you might as well
pack up the office...
And head for the hills.
Yeah.
Did your young man find
what he was looking for
over at Janie's
apartment the other day?
Yes.
It's all yours.
You're giving it to me?
Well, isn't that
why you're here?
Well, it was on my list, yeah.
Look, Ben, I know
I'm still a suspect,
but I do have an alibi, so
I figured that if I help you,
you will try to keep
my name out of the trial.
Do we have a deal?
Well, it depends on
how airtight your alibi is.
Well, when this murder
allegedly occurred,
I was being interviewed
on Channel Four... live.
Airtight?
Vacuum sealed.
Look, Ben, I think there's
something on this tape
that you should listen to.
Uh, did you know that one of
Janie's clients was a minister?
Reverend Morley Phelps.
Yeah, well, it appears
that, uh, Reverend
Phelps had quite a secret.
How many times must I
apologize to you, Janie?
Apologies aren't going to
bring back my sister, Reverend.
You can't hold me responsible
for what happened to her.
You're a murderer, a
cold-blooded murderer.
I've done nothing wrong.
You were seeing Janie Ladd.
What would your
congregation think
if they found out about that?
Janie Ladd was a human being.
I feel a great deal of
shame and remorse
about my relationship with her.
Janie made an audiotape of a
conversation she had with you
and she was using
it to blackmail you
into talking to Ann
Rawls on her behalf.
What did she think
you did to her sister?
I don't have to answer that.
She accused you of
murdering her sister.
That's a very serious charge.
If I were you, I'd
want to clarify that.
You're not saying I killed her?
Mr. Matlock, I am a man of God.
I'm sorry, Reverend.
I'll have to ask you
where you were that night.
I was here, reading Scripture.
As God is my witness.
You called today,
wanting to know
about Janie Ladd's sister.
Uh, she died of a drug
overdose about ten years ago.
- Um...
- Suicide?
- Yeah, that's what Janie said.
- Oh.
Well, thank you for
telling me about it.
But you...
you didn't have to make a
whole special trip out here.
I like to come here.
Oh.
You look real tired.
- Mmm.
- Long day?
Long, long... long day.
Stiff neck?
Yeah. Mm-hmm. Yeah.
Let me help.
Ooh.
You are tight.
Relax.
Come on, loosen up.
Put your head back.
Mmm.
Now, how does that feel?
Ah... feels good.
Take your shirt off, and...
I'll do your back.
Uh... oh, no.
No, no.
Boy, I feel... better already.
Yes.
And it's getting
really late, and my...
boy, my neck feels better.
Well, uh, maybe you can rest.
- Yeah.
- Mmm.
- Well, next time,
as the saying goes, -
will it be your place or mine?
What are you talking about?
- Don't be so innocent.
- Miss Rawls,
it was never my intention
that... that this be anything
except a strictly
business relationship.
Oh, I know.
But it happens all the time.
It's not unusual for
a client to fall in love
with her attorney.
Are you saying that you're...
in love with me?
Well, not yet.
But I do like you.
I like you an awful lot, Benji.
Oh, this is crazy.
This is just...
this is just crazy.
Why?
Why can't you and I be friends?
I mean, really good friends.
Well, for one... for
one thing, I, uh...
I don't particularly like
what you do for a living.
I could give it up.
What?
Well, I always said that if
the right man came
along, I could give it up.
Oh, no, this is crazy.
No.
- No, it's crazy.
- Well,
- No, it's...
- crazy as it sounds,
I could really make you happy.
What do you say?
Think about it, Benji.
Okay?
Don't call me Benji.
Wasn't that the name
of a dog in a movie?
Mm-hmm.
Dog!
You have two minutes, and
then I want you out of here.
Dominick, this is Miss Thomas,
the lawyer I told you about.
Nice to meet you.
I know this is an invasion
of your privacy, Mr. Sinclair...
I apologize for that...
But I just need to
confirm a few things.
I understand.
I've apprised Dominick
of the situation.
Why don't you sit down?
Mr. Sinclair, you're a private
patient of Dr. Campbell's?
Yes, I am.
I need to ask you
a few questions
about the evening of June 10.
Do you remember how
you spent that evening?
Yes, I was at home all
evening with my wife.
Do you recall speaking
with Dr. Campbell?
Quite clearly.
We spoke for the
better part of 20 minutes.
- What time was that?
- 6:30.
Could it possibly have been...
6:15? Or maybe later... 6:45?
No, I have a favorite news show
that I watch on Thursdays,
and it ends at 6:30.
I remember Dr. Campbell
called right after I turned it off.
Well, I guess that
just about covers it.
Thank you for your
time, Mr. Sinclair.
I'll walk you out.
Dominick, one second.
Well, Conrad...
I believe we're closing in.
Yes, sir. I believe
we're closing in.
You think it's the
preacher, huh?
Yeah, I'm kind of sorry,
but I think it's the preacher.
Uh, Miss Hawkins,
would you get that?
You want me to go with you?
No, I'll handle it.
Oh, thank you.
This just came.
Yeah?
Huh.
Thanks.
What in the world?
Ah.
Oh.
Pajamas.
And silk.
Yeah. Well, who in the world...?
"Benji, I have a matching pair.
"Wouldn't it be nice
if they got together?
Ann."
You tell anybody
about this, I'll kill you.
♪♪
Auggie, Ben Matlock.
Tell Bob Brooks I got to
speak with him right away.
Haven't you
anything better to do
than follow me
around, Mr. Matlock?
Well...
What, uh... what
are you doing here?
I'm packing some
of Janie's things.
Do the police know
you have a key?
Okay, Mr. Matlock.
You want to know how
I got a key to this place.
I got a key from the only
person Janie gave one to.
She lives in Italy.
She does now. She didn't always.
What do you know
about Janie's mother?
I was married to her.
Janie was your daughter?
As was Pamela.
Why didn't you
tell me this before?
I'm a minister, Mr. Matlock.
What am I supposed to tell you?
That my... my daughter, who...
who happened to make a living
sleeping with men,
hated me so bad
that she made me pay her
$300 an hour just to talk to her?
Why did she hate you?
When my daughters
were growing up, I drank.
I was violent, abusive.
One day, when Janie
was 16 and Pamela was 14,
I came home, and my wife
and daughters were gone.
Her lawyer handed
me a restraining order.
That insured that I'd never
go around them again.
18 months later, my
ex-wife called me and said
that Pamela had swallowed
a bottle of sleeping pills.
And Janie blamed you.
She swore she'd
never talk to me again.
And then, four years
ago, my entire life changed.
I found God.
I embraced the church.
I became a minister.
And I made a personal commitment
to make things right with Janie.
Uh, she said that, uh,
if I wanted to see her...
I'd, uh, have to
pay for her time...
uh, just like every
other man in her life.
Ben, everything all right?
Uh, yeah. Yeah.
B-Bob, I'm... I'm sorry
to get you out here.
It was a false alarm.
Wrong guy?
Yeah.
Mr. Ginsberg.
Ah. Miss, um... Thomas.
- Yes.
- Yeah, what can I do for you?
Would you happen
to remember if you
were working here
the evening of June 10?
It was a Thursday.
Oh, I'm here every Thursday.
Well, was Dr. Campbell
working that evening?
Sure. He's never missed a show.
Although, he did miss
our dinner that night.
He went home with the flu.
Uh, every Thursday
after the show,
we have dinner to
rehash the week.
But that Thursday,
Dr. Campbell went home sick.
Yeah, so I got to,
uh, order in Chinese
and watch the Braves
game on television.
I called him between
innings to see how he was.
And how was he?
Beats me.
It's hard to imagine, Ben.
A daughter charging her
father money just to talk with her.
Yeah.
You ready?
Yeah. Uh, could I use the phone?
I need to see if
Conrad's looking for me.
Sure. There's a
portable in the kitchen.
Yeah. Okay.
Oh.
Um...
Dr. Campbell,
I understand that your talk show
is one of the most popular
radio programs in all of Atlanta.
We have a very loyal following.
Boy, the-the calls your
listeners, uh, send in
for all the world to hear.
I mean, uh, drug problems,
sexual problems,
marital problems.
They must have a
lot of respect for you.
I certainly hope so.
I guess that's, uh...
that's, uh, very important in
your line of work... respect.
I mean, if-if a patient
didn't have respect
for his psychologist
and his opinion,
I guess he might as well
just go somewheres else then.
I have suggested that
on several occasions.
Yeah.
Uh, Doctor, uh... did
you know Janie Ladd?
Yes, I did.
How would you describe
your relationship with her?
We were friends.
Mm-hmm. Actually, you paid her
to have sexual
relations with you
for over two years, didn't you?
Yes, that is true,
but we were friends.
Hmm.
Dr. Campbell, you're a
married man and a psychologist.
When your patients find out
that this man that they
held in such high regard
was not only an adulterer,
but solicited prostitutes,
that's gonna knock a hole
right in your business, isn't it?
Objection.
Calls for speculation.
Sustained.
According to the, uh, coroner,
Janie Ladd was killed around...
6:30 on the evening
of June the tenth.
Where were you at that time?
I normally go out on Thursdays
with the station
manager, Bert Ginsberg...
But not that night?
No. I wasn't feeling well,
so I thought I should
get a good night's sleep.
Oh, yeah. How far is your
house from the station?
20 minutes.
About 20 minutes. So about 6:20.
- Mm.
- Did you go straight to bed?
No. No. I, uh...
I made some phone
calls to patients.
Uh, I was on the
phone for quite a while.
Oh. Oh, you remember
who you were on the phone to
from say, oh, 6:30
to quarter to 7:00?
Yes, I do. Dominick Sinclair.
Mr. Sinclair was kind enough
to authorize me
to reveal his name.
Mm-hmm.
And your associate
talked to him.
Hmm. That's right,
and Mr. Sinclair
did confirm that you
were on the phone with him
at the time you said.
I'm aware of that.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
Uh, his house is pretty
close to yours, isn't it?
Well, just about
a couple blocks.
Yeah, so, there'd be no
telephone record of that call
'cause it's a local
call, isn't that right?
Well... I mean, Dominick said
that he-he talked to me at 6:30.
You know that already.
Yeah, yeah, we-we know that.
We know that you spoke
to him on a telephone.
We don't know that
you spoke to him
on your phone from your house.
For crying out loud.
You know, Mr. Ginsberg,
your station manager at, uh...
WRQE is a very caring man,
and when you left
work sick that day,
he was concerned
about your health,
and he called you three times
to see how you were feeling.
And here...
Here's the telephone
bill... Blown up, of course...
For the radio station
for the month of June.
I've circled three numbers.
They're all the same.
You recognize that number?
It's my home number.
Yeah. Yeah.
And Mr. Ginsberg
is prepared to testify
that he called that number
three times that evening,
and each time, he got your
answer machine and hung up.
Why wasn't he able to get you?
You have only the one line
coming into your
house, don't you?
Yes. Uh...
Yeah, but something's looking
very, very wrong here, see.
Look at the times.
Something's very
wrong. Look here.
He called at 6:32
p.m., 6:44, 6:56.
I mean, if you... If
you were on the phone
from, say, uh,
6:30 to almost 7:00,
just the one line
coming into your house,
shouldn't he have
gotten a busy signal?
I don't know. Maybe, uh...
Maybe Mr. Sinclair and I
were a little off about the time.
I-I could have been
taking a shower.
I always put the machine
on when I go into the shower.
I don't think so.
I think you called
him at exactly 6:30,
only you didn't call
him from your house.
You called him from
Janie Ladd's apartment.
- What?
- Your Honor... this telephone
was taken from Janie
Ladd's apartment
by Atlanta Police
Detective Bob Brooks
with a warrant.
I ask that it be marked
exhibit J for identification.
It shall be marked.
Thank you.
Now, Dr. Campbell, I don't
know how familiar you are
with these new portable phones
and all of their...
fancy little gadgets here.
I mean, a lot of 'em...
I don't understand.
Page... I got that here.
And mute and-and
memory, and then,
here's, uh... What's...?
I-I got to get-get some glass...
Wha-what's that
right there? See?
Redial?
Re-Redial. Now...
Now what do you
suppose that function does?
My wife never wanted to
get one of these new things.
Yeah. Yeah.
What it does... It
automatically calls
the last number that was dialed.
And, uh, uh, a few days ago,
uh, Detective, uh,
Bob Brooks and I
were at Janie Ladd's apartment,
and I punched
this redial number.
And guess what I got?
555-7793.
You know whose number that is?
That's... Dominick
Sinclair's number.
Now, how did Mr. Sinclair's
number get programmed
into her telephone?
I don't have any idea.
You know... You
know, right-right after...
shortly after she was killed,
the police taped off
her whole apartment
so that nobody could mess
with any of the evidence.
And they put signs
on the telephones.
"Do not use."
You know what
that means, Doctor?
That means, the last call
that was made on this
phone before the police arrived
was to Dominick Sinclair.
How did his number
get in this telephone?
He didn't know Miss Ladd.
You made that call to
Mr. Sinclair on this telephone.
You made that call after you
killed Janie Ladd, didn't you?
No. That is absolutely not true.
Oh, I think it is.
You left your radio
station at 6:00,
arrived at her apartment
some 20 minutes later,
killed her, called
Dominick Sinclair,
knowing full well that
calls from her apartment,
your house to his
house, were all local calls,
and the police
would never trace 'em
'cause there wouldn't
be a record of them.
Unfortunately for
you... there is a record.
Mr. Sinclair
is right here. He's not at home.
He can't answer his phone.
I'm gonna press
the redial button.
Hello. This is
Dominick Sinclair.
I can't come to the
phone right now,
but if you'll leave a
message after the tone,
I'll give you a call right back.
The defense rests.
We find the defendant,
Ann Rawls, not guilty.
Thank you, ladies and
gentlemen of the jury.
You're dismissed.
This court is adjourned.
Thank you, Benji.
Call me.
I am free this entire weekend.
À bientôt.
It's French.
Means the check's in the mail.
www.tvsubtitles.net